CARLOS SANTANA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CARLOSSANTANA3279@GMAIL.COM | CARLOSSANTANA3279.GITHUB.IO

📞 905-807-3279 🔥 <u>GITHUB</u> 🛮 in <u>LINKEDIN</u>

PROFILE

I am a software developer with 3+ years of professional experience. My passion is to create software that improves the lives of its users. I am a diligent worker and a loyal team player. I am motivated, self-driven, and committed to continuous self-improvement.

EDUCATION

MCMASTER UNIVERSITY 2014-2019 Hamilton, ON GPA: A-

Bachelor of Applied Science Honours Computer Science (with Co-op)

SOFTWARE PROJECTS

TOUCH ROULETTE - DECISION MAKER

- Android app developed using Corona SDK and Lua
- 1 Million+ downloads on Google Play
- App to help a group of friends make decisions quickly in a fun way

PILLBOX

- Cross platform hybrid app for scheduling and tracking medications
- Built with Angular, Ionic, TypeScript in a group of 3 people
- Designed .Net Core Restful API
- Helped deliver 25+ page SRS document

EXPERIENCE

DEMANDHUB **May 2019-Now** Full Stack Developer

REACT, NODE, HTML, CSS, MYSQL

- Plan, design, and implement features for front-end web-applications and backend REST API
- Work closely with team members in other functions, including sales, support, and marketing

BELL CANADA May 2017 - Aug 2018 Software Developer (Co-op)

C#, .NET Core, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL

- Designed, developed, and maintained inhouse web tools focused on automation and analytics (Full Stack)
- Worked in 5-person DevOps team utilizing scrum and agile
- Scrum Master for 6 months (in addition to development work)

REFERENCES

Dhawal Rank

Lead Full Stack Developer - Briq Team Member at DemandHub

Dylan McIntyre

Software Engineer - Amazon Team Member at Bell

Pasindu Gunasekara

Software Engineer - Microsoft Character Reference